The deepest hidden easter egg in the nuclear power plant, who is this person? I am Haotian,
Today, I will take my brothers to unlock limited collections in one minute.
1. The preparation stage requires that you or your good friend already owns a drone.
After assembling, take the drone into the track and remember not to use it immediately after landing.
2. For the game, just choose the regular mode of S Three Nuclear Power Plant. The secret war preparation is high. In case of being defeated,
The gain outweighs the loss. 3. How to obtain this is also the most important step.
Go to the pipe above the seawater treatment area and the entrance to the underground ventilation pipe.
Release the drone into the pipe and avoid the waterlogged area, otherwise the drone will short-circuit due to water exposure.
Then he controlled the drone to arrive at the outside of the Easter Egg Room, deciphered the Morse code on the ground, and obtained four random codes.
This is more difficult to distinguish. The main bag also helps you find patterns corresponding to numbers.
Just take screenshots to correspond. Then open the first door.
In the second secret room, if you enter the fixed password 091, you can pick up the red plot note in the box.
But it is not over. The mission requirement is that the hostages must be carried to the evacuation point, and the evacuation can only be successful.
Therefore, we still need to guard against the enemy while carrying the hostages and moving forward. But the nuclear power plant map is too large.
If the evacuation point is far away, you can take over the decontamination vehicle in advance to clear the way and use the vehicle to escort the hostages.
Save energy on the road.
Four precautions: The drone will be directly damaged if it encounters water. The entire team only has five opportunities to control the drone.
The note must be carried, and the hostage must be successfully evacuated to unlock the reward.
So the risks along the way are also huge. When the evidence hostage successfully stepped out of the evacuation area,
The gift of the brave is now unlocked. Two limited collaboration figures and exclusive drone collections are all available.
Hurry up and take advantage of the main package guide and take advantage of the event window to unlock this exclusive Easter egg benefit!